Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
"The Heart of Observer #9."
Do Automata Dream of Electric Sheep?
I, Robot
Flow My Tears, the Automata Said
The Heart of Observer #9
Episode 9
Clockwork Prisoner
That girl was waving
A bright red scarf
Who do you think it was for?
Whoever it was
It doesn’t matter
Let each think it was for him
The hearts of men beginning a journey
Want a piece of romance
A bright red scarf